I eat vegetables
野菜を食べます
I have eaten fruit
果物を食べました
You asked me to eat the whole stock, and I also ate it.
出汁を全部食べてくださいと言われ、私も食べました。
You said protein, I also eat
プロテインって言ってた、私も食べます
Then why is my health not as good as yours
では、なぜ私の健康状態はあなたのほど良くないのでしょうか
that difference
その違い
That small difference means
その小さな違いが意味するのは、
Now this bento has too few vegetables
さて、このお弁当は野菜が少なすぎます
not enough protein
タンパク質が足りない
what is rice
米とは何ですか
So I'm going to correct it
それでは修正していきます
i go home at night
夜には家に帰ります
I just eat back the vegetables I don't have enough
足りない野菜だけ食べます
The fruit I didn't have enough also came back
足りなかった果物も戻ってきました
Then he gave me rice
それから彼は私にご飯をくれました
bring some of that
それの一部を持ってきてください
Wheat with Sprouts for Sprinkling
ふりかけ用もやし小麦
I'll just make a small change
ちょっとした変更を加えるだけです
Your body is different from others
あなたの体は他の人とは違います
Another aspect of vitality is weakness
活力のもう一つの側面は弱さです
this weakness and incapacity
この弱さと無力さ
and geriatric syndrome
と老人症候群
this phenomenon
この現象
so you might be clearer
そうすればもっと明確になるかもしれません
how to make quotation
見積書の作り方
Enough to live with such vitality
そんな活力で生きていけるほど
That's another
さらに、それは
compare against us
私たちと比較してください
There may be some younger
もっと若い人もいるかもしれない
Learn about the aging process
老化のプロセスについて学ぶ
Changes in our bodies and our bodies
私たちの体と体の変化
younger after middle age
中年以降は若い
you can think at this time
この時点で考えることができます
how do i keep healthy
どうすれば健康を保てますか
So I'll come to Citation in the future
だから私は将来引用に来ます
I can be at my best
私は最高の状態になれる
Frailty and disability and geriatric syndrome
フレイルと障害と老人症候群
Let me tell you about us alone
私たちだけについて話しましょう
How do we humans enter into a disability
私たち人間はどのようにして障害に陥るのか
or a weakened state
もしくは弱った状態
And this incapacity and weakness
そしてこの無力さと弱さ
what kind of relationship
どのような関係ですか
So you know what we're talking about today
それで、今日私たちが何について話しているのか知っていますか
geriatric syndrome
老人症候群
In fact, it is not a person in his fifties or sixties.
実際には50代や60代の人ではありません。
problems encountered
遭遇した問題
that you have been very healthy all your life
あなたは今までずっととても健康だったということ
no cardiovascular disease
心血管疾患がないこと
nothing sick
何も病気ではありません
a situation you will also encounter
あなたも遭遇するであろう状況
This diagram shows that one of us
この図は、私たちの一人が
a state of aging
老化の状態
The one who maintains better is this red thread
より良く維持するのはこの赤い糸です
stay level all the time
常に水平を保つ
But if a person with a lot of pain
しかし、痛みが強い人であれば、
He's always following this curve
彼はよくこのカーブを歩きます
In other words, his function declined rapidly.
言い換えれば、彼の機能は急速に低下しました。
not too old
あまり古くない
into a state of weakness
衰弱状態に陥る
So because he is in a weakened state
それで、彼は衰弱した状態にあるので、
It is easy to re-enter incapacitation
再び無力状態に陥りやすい
to this final stage of life
人生のこの最終段階へ
stay as strong as possible
できるだけ強くいてください
active state
アクティブ状態
Then stay at that red line up to the max
次に、その赤い線を最大限まで維持します
This time of life maintains a final stage
人生のこの時期は最終段階を維持します
peak state
ピーク状態
good month long month
月久月好
Then if what is going to drop is in a very short time
そして、もしそれが非常に短期間に落ちるとしたら
if it falls like this
このまま落ちたら
has entered a state of weakness
衰弱状態に入った
can you still reply
まだ返信できますか
actually it is possible
実際にそれは可能です
you can still work hard
まだ頑張れるよ
Let your function curve
関数を曲線にしてみましょう
come back to the top
トップに戻ってください
Those who rub a little don't be discouraged
ちょっと擦った人も落ち込まないでください
ok can use some
わかりました、いくつか使ってもいいですか
way of life style of life
ライフスタイル ライフスタイル
let you reply
返信させてください
Then you walk in a
それからあなたは中を歩きます
very good one
とても良いもの
on the road to health
健康への道の途中で
That frailty is often associated with chronic disease
その虚弱さは慢性疾患と関連していることが多い
are closely related
密接に関係している
may cause disability
障害を引き起こす可能性があります
observed an old man
老人を観察した
Usually we say that it is not good for people to be fat
普通、太っているのは良くないと言われますが、
But if you are already fat
しかし、すでに太っている場合は、
If you observe a fat old man
太った老人を観察していたら
suddenly lost weight
急に体重が減った
just a warning sign
ただの警告サイン
It's a warning sign of weakness
それは弱さの警告サインです
sudden weight loss
突然の体重減少
often feel exhausted
しばしば疲れを感じる
hand grip is strong enough
ハンドグリップは十分な強度があります
I have no strength to hold things
物を掴む力がない
I don't want to go out
外出したくない
I was going for a walk
散歩に行くつもりだった
no more walks now
もう散歩はしない
I don't do some things normally
普段はやらないこともある
walking?
歩いていますか？
slower and slower
どんどん遅くなる
These phenomena are called asthenia
これらの現象は無力症と呼ばれます
Basically this is a
基本的にこれは
Elderly Health Issues
高齢者の健康問題
so i'm talking about
だから私が話しているのは
It's really full of problems behind
背後には本当に問題がいっぱいです
but i think
しかし、私は思います
People in their fifties and sixties
50代、60代の人たち
should start to understand
理解し始めるべきだ
solve the problem
問題を解く
Even people in their thirties and forties
30代、40代の方でも
you can also follow
フォローすることもできます
It can also help your own family
自分の家族も助けることができる
old man inside
中の老人
Weak hand grip
手握力過弱
walking too slowly
歩くのが遅すぎる
weight loss
減量
always feel tired
いつも疲れを感じている
decreased physical activity
身体活動の減少
I don't have the strength and don't want to go out to do it
体力がないので外に出たくない
three is called weakness
３つは弱さという
then one or two words
それから一言か二言
pre-frailty
プレフレイル
In fact, people over the age of sixty-five
実は65歳以上の人は、
we look like this
私たちはこう見えます
That is, 60% of them already have
つまり、60％の人がすでに持っているということです。
A phenomenon of more than one weakening
複数が弱体化する現象
This course of debilitation develops
この衰弱の経過は進行します
generally considered
一般的に考えられている
genetic and environmental factors
遺伝的要因と環境的要因
It's all related
それはすべて関連しています
And these factors
そしてこれらの要因
other common interactions
その他の一般的なやり取り
will cause some of our body
私たちの体の一部に影響を与えるでしょう
cell damage
細胞の損傷
or a lesion at some molecular level
または何らかの分子レベルでの病変
This damage affects
このダメージが影響するのは、
multiple system organs
複数の系統の器官
drop in some functionality
いくつかの機能を追加する
Contains the brain
脳が入っている
endocrine
内分泌
immunity
免疫
muscle heart
筋肉の心臓
Blood vessel
血管
breathing kidney etc.
呼吸腎臓など
after this drop
この下落の後
If not properly such
適切にそのようなものでなければ
a lifestyle
ライフスタイル
good nutrition
良い栄養
and with
そして
Proper physical activity to maintain your body's muscles
体の筋肉を維持するための適切な身体活動
and cell function
そして細胞機能
It is easy to develop symptoms of decline
衰弱症状が出やすい
This is what I just mentioned
これは私が今言ったことです
when accidents happen
事故が起こったとき
Metabolic Syndrome
メタボリック・シンドローム
I think old people just shouldn't eat too much protein
老人はたんぱく質をあまり食べるべきではないと思う
The burden on the kidneys is too heavy
腎臓への負担が大きすぎる
but i know
しかし私は知っている
This means that many people have such a concept
そういう概念を持っている人が多いということです
That is to say, the elderly should not eat too much protein
つまり、高齢者はタンパク質を過剰に摂取すべきではありません
May be physically taxing
肉体的に負担がかかる可能性がある
Then I want to tell you that
それから私はあなたにそれを言いたいです
current scientific literature
現在の科学文献
Is supporting protein and burning medicine officially
プロテインと燃焼薬を正式にサポート
interrelated
相互に関連する
It's probably an egg balancing study
おそらく卵のバランスの研究です
that is, discussing a person
つまり、人について議論することです
how much protein do i give him
彼にどのくらいのプロテインを与えればよいですか
and see how much he excretes
そして彼がどれだけ排泄するかを見てください
Take one more point and the balance will be reached
あと1点取ればバランスが取れます
Most of these studies
これらの研究のほとんどは
Of course there are now
もちろん今もありますよ
So in order to understand
だから理解するには
How much protein do Taiwanese need to eat?
台湾人はどのくらいのたんぱく質を摂取する必要があるのでしょうか？
This method is to say
この方法はつまり、
AI for Nutrients
栄養素のための AI
AI is the so-called appropriate intake
AIはいわゆる適正摂取です
this is a method
これは方法です
This method is acceptable in nutrition
この方法は栄養学の分野で受け入れられます
it means
その意味は
If you do not have the appropriate data
適切なデータがない場合
you just grade
あなたは採点するだけです
those who have no problem at all
全く問題ない人
how much does he eat
彼はどれくらい食べますか
Thoughts on this nutrition survey
今回の栄養調査への思い
let's do the math
計算してみましょう
We just divide the elderly into
高齢者を次のように分けるだけです
non-attenuated attenuated preamplifier and attenuated
非減衰型 減衰型プリアンプおよび減衰型
to see
見る
Just look at the data on the right.
右側のデータを見てください。
These elderly people without debilitating diseases
衰弱性疾患のないこれらの高齢者
what is his protein intake
彼のタンパク質摂取量はどれくらいですか
we see yes
そうだね
1.21 per kilogram of body weight
体重1kgあたり1.21
1.22 for men and women
男性と女性の場合 1.22
This is a mesogastric
これは胃間膜です
What does mesogastric mean?
中胃ってどういう意味ですか？
is the most people
が一番多いです
people here
ここの人たち
Most of these people are uptake
これらの人々のほとんどは摂取しています
we can see the debilitated
私たちは衰弱しているのを見ることができます
Eat less than one gram per kilogram of body weight a day
1日の食事量は体重1kgあたり1g未満にしましょう
Pre-failure is centered
事前障害が中心にあります
Then this number may not mean anything to you
そうすると、この数字はあなたにとって何の意味もないかもしれません
Maybe you see this number and feel nothing
もしかしたらこの数字を見ても何も感じないかもしれません
but i want to tell you
でも、あなたに言いたいのです
Global Recommendations for Protein
プロテインに関する世界的な推奨事項
almost all have a number
ほぼ全員に番号が付いています
That number is 1.2
その数字は1.2です
an old man a day
一日老人
He needs to eat 1.2 grams per kilogram of body weight
体重1kgあたり1.2gを食べる必要がある
you can eat like this
このように食べることができます
The American-Japanese Diet Guide
アメリカと日本の食事ガイド
it is calculated after semen
精液の後に計算されます
That is, if you keep eating
つまり食べ続けると
All your nutrients will be up to standard
すべての栄養素が基準を満たすようになります
But among
しかし、その中では
When middle-aged people are doing this
中高年がこれをやっていると
No one knows that the old man Meigong needs to eat 1.2 grams
美公老人が1.2グラムを食べる必要があることを誰も知りません
19 to 34 years old
19歳～34歳
If he eats such 1850 calories
1850カロリーも食べたら
Or he eats 2150 to above
あるいは2150以上食べる
Is his agent worth enough?
彼のエージェントには十分な価値があるだろうか？
Enough 1kg 1.2g is really difficult to produce
十分な1kg 1.2gを生産するのは本当に困難です
Even a 71-year-old
71歳でも
If he eats 1650 calories he will be enough
1650カロリー食べれば十分だろう
But we found that
しかし、私たちはそれを発見しました
What if it's on the women's side?
それが女性側だったらどうなるでしょうか？
From young women he has some who eat very little
若い女性の中には、ほとんど食べない人もいる
1450 calories only
1450カロリーのみ
Some women in their 70s
70代の女性もいる
Only eat 1300 calories
1300カロリーだけ食べる
So for those who are older and eat less
したがって、高齢で食べる量が少ない人にとっては、
His sales value is not enough
彼の販売価値は十分ではありません
Usually there is a general rule
通常は一般的なルールがあります
That is if you eat very little people
それはあなたが食べる人をほんの少ししか食べない場合です
you are prone to malnutrition
あなたは栄養失調になりやすいです
If the entrusted sales value is not enough, it will enter into decline
委託販売額が足りなければ衰退に転じる
this stage
この段階
talk to the government
政府と話す
you for people who eat less
あなたは食べる量が少ない人のために
This dietary advice needs to be modified
この食事に関するアドバイスは修正する必要があります
otherwise
さもないと
These people may fall into the proxy for insufficient value
これらの人々は、価値が不十分なために代理人に陥る可能性があります
Especially the camp French
特にキャンプフレンチ
Internationally, the most concerned is consignment sales
海外で最も懸念されるのは委託販売
to address the weakness
弱点に対処するために
Frailty is not only related to protein
フレイルはたんぱく質だけが関係しているわけではない
Is it not related to other nutrients?
他の栄養素は関係ないのでしょうか？
We found in the literature
文献で見つけました
I saw that it is related to many trace elements
多くの微量元素に関係していることが分かりました
And it seems that there is a phenomenon that
と言う現象があるようです。
Nutrient deficient items
栄養不足の品目
more words
もっと言葉を
the greater the chance that the person is debilitated
その人が衰弱している可能性が高くなります
other than protein
プロテイン以外の
lack of literature
文献の不足
B12 deficiency
B12欠乏症
lack of C
Cが不足している
new lack
新たな不足
have some correlation
何らかの相関関係がある
One conjecture might be that
一つの推測としては、
Is it just eating too little?
ただ食べる量が少ないだけなのでしょうか？
So let's explore further
それではさらに詳しく調べてみましょう
If an old man in Taiwan has debilitating disease,
台湾の老人が衰弱性の病気にかかったら、
his overall diet
彼の全体的な食事
what is it like
それはどんな感じですか
then let me tell you
それなら教えてあげましょう
This is male data
こちらは男性のデータです
people with different heat
違う熱量を持った人たち
he is different
彼は違う
Six categories of this proposal
この提案の6つのカテゴリー
What are the six categories of recommendations?
推奨事項の 6 つのカテゴリとは何ですか?
Usually when making dietary advice
通常、食事に関するアドバイスをするときは、
or divide food into six broad categories
または食品を6つの大まかなカテゴリーに分類する
It means that you have to eat these six categories
この6つのカテゴリーを食べなければならないということです
And your six categories of food
そしてあなたの6つの食べ物カテゴリー
If you eat the portion I suggest you
あなたがその部分を食べるなら、私はあなたに勧めます
You have enough nutrients
栄養は十分にありますよ
What about when your calories are low?
カロリーが低いときはどうですか？
Your six categories of advice are less
あなたの6つのカテゴリーのアドバイスは少なくなります
Then the whole stock here is our staple food.
そして、ここにあるストック全体が私たちの主食になります。
That is to say, it is suggested that three bowls of rice may be enough
つまり、ご飯は茶わん3杯で十分だということです。
But we noticed that these poor people eat a lot
しかし、私たちはこれらの貧しい人々がたくさん食べることに気づきました
He only needs three bowls
彼にはボウルが 3 つしか必要ない
But he ate three and a half bowls a day
しかし、彼は一日に3杯半食べました
A normal person eats a little less than what he should eat
普通の人は本来食べるべき量よりも少し少ない量しか食べません
But everyone sees this bean fish meat egg
でも誰もがこの豆魚肉卵を見ます
the protein
いわゆるプロテイン
All kinds of meat, eggs, seafood
あらゆる種類の肉、卵、魚介類
This poor man also eats less
この哀れな男は食べる量も減った
Normally, it is the same as the early stage of degeneration
通常は変性の初期と同じです
He is simply over the amount
彼は単に金額を超えているだけだ
But are they too much protein?
しかし、タンパク質が多すぎるのでしょうか？
Actually they don't have much protein
実はタンパク質があまり多くない
Another important source of protein is milk
もう一つの重要なタンパク質源は牛乳です
Then our people don't drink milk
そうすれば我が国の人々は牛乳を飲まなくなります
So there's a bunch of protein and a lid missing here.
つまり、ここには大量のタンパク質と蓋がありません。
So we can see that
それでわかります
If you are a person without decay
腐りのない人なら
Actually your protein is just right
実はあなたのプロテインはちょうどいいのです
The amount to eat is to put milk and this silicon together, it is just right
食べる量は牛乳とこのシリコンを混ぜるとちょうどいいです
Almost all Taiwanese
ほぼ全員が台湾人
So our bone Su Song is a big problem
だから私たちの骨スーソンは大きな問題です
For this male of these people
この人たちの中のこの男性にとって
less vegetables
野菜が少ない
Then the fruit didn't meet the standard
するとその果物は基準を満たさなかった
And there is not enough fat
そして脂肪が足りない
Because most of us young people have too much fat
私たち若者のほとんどは脂肪が多すぎるため、
but these old people
しかし、この老人たちは、
But the fat did not reach
でも脂肪は届かなかった
this grease
このグリース
The recommended amount of oil in Taiwan
台湾の推奨オイル量
the so-called five
いわゆる5人
very little
とても少ない
But the reason none of them reach is because
でも、どれも届かない理由は、
Old people dare not eat too much oil
老人は油をあまり食べないほうがいい
So it doesn't have enough calories
そうするとカロリーが足りない
so you can see
それでわかります
A Diet for Frailty
虚弱体質のための食事療法
just a little too much rice
ただご飯が少し多すぎる
Not enough eye protein
目のたんぱく質が足りない
not enough milk
ミルクが足りない
male words
男性の言葉
It seems that the vegetables and fruits are not enough
野菜や果物が足りないようです
low fat
低脂肪
so is a
それもそうだ
all kinds of things are not enough
各種東西都不太夠的
one case
1つのケース
Well, women have a similar trend
まあ、女性にも同様の傾向があります
women we see
私たちが見る女性
is its heat
その熱は
not that much of a difference
そんなに違いはない
it's basically
それは基本的にです
Eat much less than men
男性に比べて食べる量がかなり少ない
weak women too
弱い女性も
she almost ate
彼女はほとんど食べてしまいました
80% full meal
ご飯80％
Three bowls is about the same
3杯はほぼ同じ
two points
2点
Two point four bowls are enough
2.4 ボウルで十分です
But she eats almost three bowls of rice
でも彼女はご飯を3杯近く食べます
It also has less protein
たんぱく質も少ないし
I don't drink this milk
この牛乳は飲みません
fruit with little fat
脂肪分の少ない果物
rare
レア
Vegetables are eaten more
野菜がもっと食べられる
can feel
感じることができる
is protein
たんぱく質です
indeed a key
まさに鍵
Especially the food eaten by Taiwanese
特に台湾人が食べる食べ物
It's still rice
やはりご飯です
Nutrients in it
その中に含まれる栄養素
are not so rich
そんなに裕福ではない
protein doesn't seem to be enough
プロテインが足りないようです
and fat
そして脂肪
too little too few calories
カロリーが少なすぎる
These are all
これらはすべてです
Features we know
私たちが知っている機能